Do you have body wipes?
I do.
Ugh, I've got a run.
Hurry, before Yamabuki-kun gets here.
He can wait outside.
Wait, did we lock the door?
N...
No! Are you all stupid?!
What?!
How could you change
with the door unlocked?
Photos last forever in
this day and age, you know?
Aren't you high school girls?
Lock the door if it's embarrassing!
Why are we getting yelled at?
Don't ask me.
We messed up, huh?
First apologize
for walking in on us, perv!
You're the pervs for changing
without a care in the world!
Where do you get off going on
the attack after walking in on us?!
That said...
I still want to apologize
for seeing what I did! I'm sorry!
You're a real roller coaster, huh?
This is my first time
seeing someone kowtow.
Applications for gym equipment
are due this week.
That's all for the after-school broadcast.
Please take care on your way home.
That's a wrap.
I flubbed my lines again.
Let's go eat something sweet.
Want to join us, Yamabuki-kun?
Sorry, but I already have plans.
Oh, really? That's too bad.
If you're going to cry about it,
I can join you remotely.
Sorry, I don't feel
that strongly about it.
Be seeing you, then.
Guess it's just the four of us.
I want ice cream.
What's up, Nene-chan?
Let's tail him.
Huh?
Where'd that come from?
I mean, he saw us half-naked!
It won't be fair unless we get to
see him in a compromising position, too!
If we tail him, I'm sure
he'll slip up somewhere.
It wasn't that embarrassing for me.
Yeah, because you were hidden behind me!
He pretty much saw me
in my birthday avatar!
Is this the right thing to do, though?
It does sound fun.
I am kinda interested in his private life.
Okay, that's three against one.
We have a majority.
The "Catch Yamabuki with
His Pants Down" Alliance is born!
We'll get some dirt on him
and put him at our beck and call!
Can't say I'm a fan of the name.
What are you doing?
We want blackmail photos of him.
If he's reading a porn mag...
HOW TO TEACH TODDLERS JAPANESE
Well...
Doesn't look like he is.
We're pretty far out in the suburbs now.
I feel like a detective! How exciting!
You're getting into this, Shinobu.
I just know he's going to
a shady establishment!
Is he going to study?
Here we go!
He's gonna watch porn in the café!
Why are you so giddy about this?
Let's go in there.
I hope they have matcha ice cream.
What do I order?
Make sure he doesn't spot us, okay?
Where's Yamabuki-kun?
I don't see him...
Welcome.
Let me know when you're ready to order.
Okay.
Wait, why's he working here?
He's a rich kid, right?
Did he lie about his background?
Big scandal!
Yamabuki-kun.
Sorry to put you on
so many shifts this week.
If anything, I'm grateful.
I really need the money.
So he is broke.
He's a ruined noble!
Noble...?
But aren't you rich?
Not at all.
My father's the one who's rich.
I'm just a high schooler.
I try to earn the money I need by myself.
Good on you.
What's the money for, by the way?
My club's audio equipment.
I need a million yen or so.
He talked about that before.
But didn't he say he made
a million on the stock market?
Maybe he lied to us so we'd agree.
Are you sure you want to be
spending that much on a club?
True, it is just a club.
And the equipment may
be wasted on those four.
Those four?
Frankly, I was sorely
disappointed in them.
But they're trying to
change for the better.
So I want to invest in their potential.
Their voices have something
special about them.
Are you in love with them or something?
Why would you think that?
I'm speaking purely as a member
of the broadcasting club...
Excuse us!
Can you take our order?
Wha?
Why are you here?
You look good in that apron.
Stop that!
We dug up some major dirt on him.
My phone can take pics in 8K!
Shame if something happened to it!
BROADCASTING ROOM (TEMP)
Curses.
They found out about my job!
Apollo has even more
blackmail material on me!
Furin High doesn't allow part-time jobs...
Heya.
Kirino? There's still time
until the evening broadcast...
Don't tell me!
You're here to blackmail me over my job?!
I don't negotiate with criminals!
For I carry the honor
of the Yamabuki Group!
I saw an embarrassing side of you, Bucky.
It won't be fair unless I show you mine.
BROADCASTING ROOM
Hold it. Why did you just lock the door?
I mean, you said it.
"LOCK THE DOOR IF IT'S EMBARRASSING."
You keep your tablet in there?
Doesn't it get in the way?
Not really.
So, what about the tablet?
This is embarrassing to talk about,
but I figured I could ask you.
Hey, could you give me some advice?
I see. Your view count
has hit a wall recently.
SAME AS YESTERDAY - NEED MORE VARIETY
THIS IS GETTING STALE
I never got these comments before.
People might be getting bored of me.
Unsurprising.
HELLO-IKO!
YOU'RE AS CUTE AS EVER TODAY!!!
Anyone would get bored of streams
with nothing but "Hello" and "Bye."
THIS STREAM HAS ENDED
I-I only do that during break times.
Otherwise, I do karaoke, gaming,
chatting, and cooking streams.
I even do drawing streams sometimes.
I'm the one who drew
Ikon's avatar, you know?
To tell the truth, I already know
why you've hit a wall.
Huh?
I watched pretty much all
of your streams, so there's no doubt.
You watched it all? Every bit of me?
Yes. I positively devoured
everything you put out.
You super-dirty voyeur!
Wait, why? You made it all public!
It's good that you're doing a variety
of content, but take a look.
Hello-Iko. I'm Ikonic.
We've got a karaoke stream today.
Hope you enjoy it.
It's my birthday today!
Thank you for all the comments!
They really made me happy!
Eek, a zombie!
I'm really bad with horror!
I'm singing today.
Can you tell how nervous I am?
I'm in a great mood because
I did well on my exams.
Your face looks the same every time!
Not so loud.
Your avatar's too lifeless!
Can you tell how excited I am?
Like hell anyone can!
Your avatar barely qualifies as animated.
You can do so much more
with 2D drawings these days.
By altering or switching individual parts,
they can be just
as expressive as 3D models.
There's software that can
animate flat images, too.
I know that, but I suck at computer stuff.
And commissioning someone isn't cheap.
Kirino...
Who do you think the man before you is?
Errand boy.
I'd forgotten about that title.
Let yours truly handle this.
I happen to be an expert
with most computer software.
I-I'm saving so much money!
Don't say that out loud.
You've got work to do, okay?
Separate your avatar
into layers and redraw it.
We're going to be busy.
IKON 2.0 DEBUT STREAM PLANNING MEETING!
The wait is over, Kirino!
It's time to debut VTuber
Sumeragi Ikon's 2.0 model!
Behold!
I don't see anything different.
Your avatar still has the same look, yes.
But it got a major
overhaul under the hood.
It can now track your facial expressions
and display a rich variety of emotions.
Let's give it a shot. Try laughing.
Okay.
Wahaha! How amusing!
Can you maybe... put some heart into it?
I am, though.
Listen, Kirino.
Your viewers want to connect
with you on an emotional level.
You can make your avatar smile
with the click of a button,
but that's not the same.
They want to see you laugh
or get angry for real.
I always have a smile during my streams.
Yeah, but it's fake.
Show more emotion.
I can't.
I'm not good at expressing myself.
Oho?
Can you still say that when I do this?!
E-Eek!
Nobody wants a streamer
with a poker face!
They want to see your emotions explode!
Now, lay it all bare!
Stop tickling me...
I hate it!
FAIR
You just laughed, didn't you?
I'm not... laughing...
Now you're just being stubborn!
Look at me!
No!
Give it up...
That's it.
That's what your fans want to see.
You've got such a cute smile.
If you can do this on stream...
Hey, you.
What're you doing to Iko?
The door's locked, and nobody
answered when we knocked,
so we took a peek in case
someone had passed out inside.
Sorry.
Huh? Is Iko being pounced on?
Open the door already!
This will be a pain to explain.
Are you okay, Iko?!
Why are your clothes all a mess?!
It's nothing, really.
All he did was touch me all over
and then pin me to the floor.
Wha? What the heck?!
I see. It does sound bad
when you put it into words.
Japanese is such a deep language.
Yeah, you stop philosophizing right now!
I'm taking you to the police station.
I'm under arrest?!
Bucky.
Thanks for everything.
Listen, Iko.
VTubers gain popularity when
their real selves shine through.
Remember that well.
Yes, boss.
Don't worry. You were able to
put on a lovely smile.
Go out and show them what
your new avatar can do.
You got it.
I'll do my best to give my viewers
a genuine smile on tomorrow's stream.
Good. I have high hopes for you.
How can you act all cool
when you're tied up?
Whatcha watching?
Sumeragi Ikon-chan's livestream.
Apparently, she's got a new,
more expressive avatar.
SUMERAGI IKON VER. 2.0 DEBUT STREAM!
Wow, lemme see!
Hello-Iko! I'm Ikonic!
This is Sumeragi Ikon,
assertive shy girl VTuber.
Nice to meet you.
159 WATCHING NOW
Uh, I don't see much of a difference.
Hey, Iko!
Why are you even stiffer than usual?
You're making the new avatar pointless!
WHAT CHANGED?
I... I can't.
I can't do this.
"I CAN'T SMILE IN FRONT OF THE CAMERA!!"
T-Today...
I'm debuting my new avatar.
Um, thank you all for coming to watch.
How...
How do you like my new avatar?
What part of this is new, exactly?
Right?
I thought it'd be cuter.
Did she just clickbait?
You see, I drew a lot of
new art for this avatar...
She did fine just yesterday.
It's not that she can't show emotion.
She just can't do it in front of people.
Huh?
Did I mess up the settings or something?
156 WATCHING NOW
I'm such a klutz.
But I didn't expect her
to freeze up like this.
146 WATCHING NOW
O-Oh, just give me some time, guys.
Did she have a bad
experience in the past?
Oh, well. Time to start the operation.
Bye-Iko to everyone leaving.
I'm sorry.
SMILE!!
Ugh, I can't!
It feels like everyone's
staring at me up close!
121 WATCHING NOW
It's making my face go all stiff!
IS IT TIME FOR THE LAST RESORT?
IT'S SOMETHING OF A
DRASTIC MEASURE, THOUGH.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
DO YOU WANT MY HELP?
Help me.
YOU GOT IT
Huh?
And that's the stream paused.
Wait...
What?!
Whew.
Wh-What are you doing, Bucky?!
You can't just stop
a livestream like that!
People were watching!
Your viewers were dropping
like flies, anyway.
Calm down for a second.
Take a good look at yourself.
You're all sweaty from the nerves.
Take some clothes off.
You hyper-dirty perv.
Hyper is fine by me.
Just take them off before you get sick.
I'm so disappointed in you, though.
Goodness. All your big words
before the stream were just talk, huh?
You don't have to be a jerk.
I didn't think I'd get
this nervous either.
Even so, you should've been
able to smile through it.
Is that all your dream means to you?
You talk like you know it all, Bucky.
I'm serious about this, okay?
No, you aren't the least bit serious.
You're just fooling around.
I am serious, you jerk!
I kept quiet and listened,
but you're just running your mouth!
I don't know about quiet, but okay.
I'm doing my best, okay?!
I do have emotions! I'm only human!
But... But...
I can't do it! I'm too scared!
Just quit, then.
You hate streaming, don't you?
I love streaming! I don't wanna quit!
Do you love streaming that much?
What do you love about it?
Huh? Well...
I love being able to interact
with hundreds of people, and also...
Iko-chan!
What's wrong?
Don't give me that!
You didn't turn off the audio!
Your whole exchange was streamed online!
What are you doing, Iko?!
I knew it! The guy was Yamabuki!
It's all over for me.
Anyway, take a look at your stream.
No... I know I'm getting canceled.
Forget canceled.
You've got a whole wave
of people tuning in!
2,041 WATCHING NOW
Huh? Why? What's going on?
Why don't you give your
viewers an explanation?
Wait... I can't talk to so many people!
2,165 WATCHING NOW
Iko.
Yesterday, I said,
"VTubers gain popularity when
their real selves shine through."
That wasn't entirely accurate.
To be more accurate,
they gain popularity when they
accidentally reveal their true selves.
You can tell what your viewers
want to hear right now, right?
Now, go end the stream on a good note.
Forget-It-All Beam!
Whoa!
Cute!
Love the gap!
BEAM!! - GIMME MORE!
I-I'm ending the stream here!
TODAY'S STREAM HAS ENDED
SUMERAGI IKON'S PRIVATE STREAM
Iko's private stream?
Why couldn't she just call me?
Heya, Bucky. Is now a good time?
Yes. I'm just in the bathroom.
You call that a good time?
I realized I didn't thank you earlier.
So I figured I could do it
with my new avatar.
Thank me?
All I did was talk down to you.
I know what you did.
You left the stream running
and made me mad on purpose.
Whatever do you mean?
I'm still a bit scared...
But I'll try to be myself more from now.
Could be better.
Your new avatar is pretty good and all,
but it doesn't compare
to your real smile.
Hey, it went back to a poker face!
Was all our effort today in vain?
Hello? Come in!
Oh no... Hiding my face
blocks the tracking.
H-Huh? This is weird.
I thought I could smile for Bucky now...
Hey!
But when he looks at me,
my face gets hot!
"I CAN'T SMILE IN FRONT OF YOU...!"
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Sriram Gurunathan
Mariana Martinez
William Haggard
Quality Check:
Translation Check:
S Bilyeu
Michelle Tymon